drewaltizer.com 2011-11-03

# Drew Altizer Photography - San Francisco Society Photographs

This is the privacy policy (the "Policy") for the Web site currently located at www.drewaltizer.com (the "Site").  Drew Altizer Photography ("we" or "us") owns and operates the Site. Please carefully review this Policy to learn about how we collect, use and protect any Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) you provide us on or through the Site and your choices for managing your Personal Information. By using the Site, you signify your assent to this Policy. This Policy is subject to the Terms of Use posted on the Site [**TERMS OF USE**](http://drewaltizer.com/terms.php).

**Managing Personal Information**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy or wish to update or delete your Personal Information in connection with the Site, please contact us at:

Drew Altizer Photography  
San Francisco, CA  
415.376.7359  
drew@drewaltizer.com

**Information We Automatically Collect**  
We automatically collect information that does not reflect or reference an individually identifiable user ("Non-Personal Information") to help us understand how our users use the Site. For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect your IP address and other information about your Internet connectivity. In addition, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your Web browser. A "cookie" is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your Web browser from a Web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases and preferences while you are at the Site. Most Web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the Site, such as the shopping and other areas, will not function properly if you do so. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) may use cookies in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

**Information You Choose To Submit**  
We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information ("Personal Information") only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to register with the Site, subscribe to one of our services, make a purchase, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Site.

**How We Use Personal And Non-Personal Information**  
We use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for internal purposes, such as enhancing your experience at the Site; performing administration and technical support for the Site; notifying you about our new and existing content, events, products or services; and creating aggregated information about demographics and usage patterns.  
We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Policy.  
From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, marketing services, advertisement serving, Web hosting, Web development, etc. We provide our service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. This Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party may collect from you.  
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to us, to our affiliates or to others. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.  
We may use, and disclose to third parties, certain aggregated Non-Personal Information (e.g., the number of registered members who reside in a particular geographic location, etc.) without your permission.  However, such information does not identify you individually.  
In the event of a change of control transaction, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in connection with such transaction. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit Personal Information and Non-Personal Information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission.

**Security**  
We use industry standard security measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site, and you do so at your own risk.

**Policies For Minors**  
The safety of children online is very important to us. We encourage parents to spend time online with their children and to review the Web sites accessed by their children.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a user under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

**Policy Changes**  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Those changes will go into effect on the Effective Date disclosed at the end of the changed Policy. The new Policy will apply to all current and past users of the Site and will replace any prior Policies that are inconsistent.

**Effective Date** :  August 10, 2008
